Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 5: Boxes 89-101
Archives Information File, Section 5: Boxes 89-101
- Box: 98, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Wages and Hours in Children's Camps, 1960; Publication (Box 98, Folder 17)
    Notes: Summer 1960
- Box: 98, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Money and Real Wages in India, Publication (Box 98, Folder 18)
    Author: Shri Ram Centre Press
- Box: 98, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Insurance Industry Salary Survey, 1962; Publication (Box 98, Folder 19)
    Notes: October 1962
- Box: 98, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Retribuzione e Costo del Lavoro, Publication (Box 98, Folder 20)
    Author: Associazione Industriale Lombarda
- Box: 98, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 98, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Laundries and Cleaning Services, 1963; Publication (Box 98, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Ohio Wage Earners in Laundries and Dry Cleaning Establishments, Publication (Box 98, Folder 21)
    Author: Amy G. Maher
- Box: 98, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 98, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Laundries & Cleaning Services, 1966; Publication (Box 98, Folder 22)
- Box: 98, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 98, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Laundry and Dry Cleaning Services, 1960; Publication (Box 98, Folder 23)
    Author: Pennsylvania Department of Labor and Industry
- Box: 98, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 98, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Wages in Logging and Forest Operations, 1963; Publication (Box 98, Folder 24)
    Author: G. Hazenberg
    Notes: February 1, 1963
- Box: 98, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 98, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Minnesota Wage Survey, 1950; Publication (Box 98, Folder 25)
    Notes: December 1950
- Box: 98, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 98, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Pay Data, Publication (Box 98, Folder 26)
    Author: Newark Board of Commissioners
- Box: 98, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 98, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Occupational Wage Survey, 1949; Publication (Box 98, Folder 27)
- Box: 98, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 98, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Comparison of Wages in New York City with Other Areas, Publication (Box 98, Folder 28)
    Author: New York City Department of Labor
  - Item 2: Occupational Wage Survey, 1964; Publication (Box 98, Folder 28)
- Box: 98, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 98, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: The Wage Board's Task, 1961; Publication (Box 98, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: Women Workers in New York, Publication (Box 98, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: Wages and Hours in Selected Personal Services, 1962; Publication (Box 98, Folder 29)
    Notes: June 1962
  - Item 4: Wages and Hours in Industries Covered by the Minimum Wage Law, Publication (Box 98, Folder 29)
  - Item 5: Distribution of Manufacturing Production Workers by Plant Gross Average Hourly Earnings, 1955; Publication (Box 98, Folder 29)
    Notes: January 1955
- Box: 98, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 98, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Pilot Survey, Publication (Box 98, Folder 30)
    Author: Nova Scotia Department of Labour
  - Item 2: Trends in Wages, Publication (Box 98, Folder 30)
- Box: 98, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 98, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Pilot Survey, Publication (Box 98, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: Average Weekly Wages, Publication (Box 98, Folder 31)
- Box: 98, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 98, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Occupational Wage Survey, 1968; Publication (Box 98, Folder 32)
    Author: Oklahoma Employment Security Commission
    Notes: October 1968
- Box: 98, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 98, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Wages and Hours in Nonprofit Homes, 1962; Publication (Box 98, Folder 33)
- Box: 98, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 98, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Industrial Wage Survey, 1967; Publication (Box 98, Folder 34)
    Author: New Brunswick Department of Labour
    Notes: April 1967
  - Item 2: Trud I Zaraliotnaia Plata, 1958; Publication (Box 98, Folder 34)
    Language: Russian.
- Box: 98, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 98, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Paints and Varnishes, 1961; Publication (Box 98, Folder 35)
    Notes: May 1961
- Box: 98, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 98, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Wages and Hours in Selected Personal Services, 1962; Publication (Box 98, Folder 36)
- Box: 98, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 98, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Occupational Wage Survey, 1949; Publication (Box 98, Folder 37)
- Box: 98, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 98, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: The Pearl Button Industry in Puerto Rico, 1947; Publication (Box 98, Folder 38)
- Box: 98, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 98, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Radio & TV Broadcasting Industry, 1950; Publication (Box 98, Folder 39)
- Box: 98, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 98, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Effects of Minimum Wage Rates, 1963; Publication (Box 98, Folder 40)
    Notes: November 1963
  - Item 2: Minimum Wages in Grocery Stores, Publication (Box 98, Folder 40)
- Box: 98, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 98, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: The Impact of Unions on Relative Wages in California Retail Food Establishments, Publication (Box 98, Folder 41)
    Author: Walter A. Fogel
  - Item 2: Wages & Hours in the Retail Drug Industry, 1965; Publication (Box 98, Folder 41)
- Box: 98, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 98, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Occupational Wage Survey, 1966; Publication (Box 98, Folder 42)
    Author: New Jersey Department of Labor and Industry
- Box: 98, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 98, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Ohio Wage-Hour Study, 1962; Publication (Box 98, Folder 43)
    Author: Ohio Department of Industrial Relations
    Notes: May 1962
- Box: 98, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 98, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: The Retailing, Wholesaling, and Warehousing Industry in Puerto Rico, 1965; Publication (Box 98, Folder 44)
- Box: 98, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 98, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Salaries of Certificated Employees in California Public Schools, 1967; Publication (Box 98, Folder 45)
    Author: Henry W. Magnuson, Peter J. Tashnovian
- Box: 98, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 98, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Salaries and Salary Policies of CASDA Schools, 1967; Publication (Box 98, Folder 46)
    Notes: November 1967
- Box: 98, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 98, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Wages and Hours in Nonpublic Schools and Colleges, 1961; Publication (Box 98, Folder 47)
    Notes: October 1961
- Box: 98, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 98, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Wages and Salaries in Seattle, 1951; Publication (Box 98, Folder 48)
    Notes: December 12, 1951
- Box: 98, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 98, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Seafaring Wage Rates, 1964; Publication (Box 98, Folder 49)
  - Item 2: Seafaring Wage Rates, 1967; Publication (Box 98, Folder 49)
  - Item 3: Seafaring Wage Rates, 1968; Publication (Box 98, Folder 49)
    Notes: December 1968
  - Item 4: Seafaring Wage Rates, 1960; Publication (Box 98, Folder 49)
    Notes: March 1, 1960
- Box: 99, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Hours and Earnings in South Carolina, 1963; Publication (Box 99, Folder 1)
    Author: South Carolina Employment Security Commission
- Box: 99, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Wage Trends in the Iron and Steel Industry, 1966; Publication (Box 99, Folder 2)
- Box: 99, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Comparitive Wage Structures, Publication (Box 99, Folder 3)
    Author: M. Gardner Clark
- Box: 99, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Estudio Economico para la Determinacion del Salario Minimo en la Industria Textil, 1965; Publication (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: The Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico, 1964; Publication (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Estudio Economico, 1966; Publication (Box 99, Folder 4)
- Box: 99, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Industria Textil, 1966; Publication (Box 99, Folder 5)
    Author: Publicaciones del SERH
- Box: 99, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Cigar Manufacturing, 1961; Publication (Box 99, Folder 6)
    Notes: April-May 1961
- Box: 99, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Pay and Conditions of Employment of Drivers, Publication (Box 99, Folder 7)
- Box: 99, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Occupational Wage Survey, 1949; Publication (Box 99, Folder 8)
- Box: 99, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Occupational Wage Survey, 1970; Publication (Box 99, Folder 9)
- Box: 99, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Hours and Earnings in Manufacturing and Nonmanufacturing, Publication (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Wage Distribution for Factory Workers, 1955; Publication (Box 99, Folder 10)
    Notes: February 1955
  - Item 3: Hourly Earnings Excluding Overtime Pay, 1957; Publication (Box 99, Folder 10)
    Notes: July 1957
  - Item 4: Statistical Materials Bearing on the Salary Requirement in Regulations Pary 541, 1947; Publication (Box 99, Folder 10)
    Notes: December 1947
- Box: 99, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Negotiated Wage Increases, Publication (Box 99, Folder 11)
    Author: Richard A. Lester
- Box: 99, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Occupational Earnings and Wage Trends in Metropolitan Areas, 1966; Publication (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Trends in Labor Compensation in the United States, Publication (Box 99, Folder 12)
- Box: 99, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Wage Developments in Manufacturing, 1962; Publication (Box 99, Folder 13)
- Box: 99, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Wage & Salary Survey, 1969; Publication (Box 99, Folder 14)
    Author: Washington State Department of Personnel
  - Item 2: Wages and Productivity in Manufacturing by Industry and State, Publication (Box 99, Folder 14)
    Author: Gerhard Bry
- Box: 99, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Wage & Salary Survey, 1968; Publication (Box 99, Folder 15)
    Author: Washington Department of Personnel
- Box: 99, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Wage Rates in Selected Occupations, 1960; Publication (Box 99, Folder 16)
    Author: West Indies Department of Statistics
- Box: 99, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Wholesale Groceries, 1965; Publication (Box 99, Folder 17)
- Box: 99, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Research in Wages, Publication (Box 99, Folder 18)
    Author: Labor Market Research Committee
- Box: 99, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Wages Councils Act, 1950; Publication (Box 99, Folder 19)
- Box: 99, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 99, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Wages in the U.S.S.R., 1960; Publication (Box 99, Folder 20)
    Author: Leonid Kostin
- Box: 99, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 99, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Minimum Wages Act, 1948; Publication (Box 99, Folder 21)
    Author: Government Central Press
- Box: 99, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 99, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Vara Loner, Publication (Box 99, Folder 22)
    Author: Hans Almgren
  - Item 2: Loneuppfoljning, Publication (Box 99, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Levnadskostnader Och Loner, 1960; Publication (Box 99, Folder 22)
    Author: Landsorganisationen I Sverige
    Notes: April 1960
- Box: 99, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 99, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Der Arbeitslohn, 1966; Publication (Box 99, Folder 23)
    Author: Buchdruckerei Flawil AG
- Box: 99, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 99, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Wages, Incomes, Rural Development, Investment and Price Policy, 1967; Publication (Box 99, Folder 24)
    Author: Tanzania Government
- Box: 99, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 99, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Wartime Regulation of Wages and Hours in Canada, 1941; Publication (Box 99, Folder 25)
- Box: 99, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 99, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The System of Wage Regulation in the Netherlands, 1957; Publication (Box 99, Folder 26)
    Author: Svensk Sparbankstidskrift
- Box: 99, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 99, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Future of Price and Wage Controls, 1952; Publication (Box 99, Folder 27)
    Author: Buel W. Patch
    Notes: December 17, 1952
  - Item 2: Selected Papers Presented Before the Labor-Management Round Table, 1952; Publication (Box 99, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: The Stabilization of Wages in the Reconversion Period, 1946; Publication (Box 99, Folder 27)
    Author: National Wage Stabilization Board
    Notes: May 1, 1946
  - Item 4: Wartime Policies, 1942; Publication (Box 99, Folder 27)
    Notes: May 1942
  - Item 5: Wage Stabilization General Orders and Interpretations, Publication (Box 99, Folder 27)
    Author: National War Labor Board
  - Item 6: Wages in a National Emergency, Publication (Box 99, Folder 27)
- Box: 99, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 99, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Basic Facts About Wage Stabilization, Publication (Box 99, Folder 28)
- Box: 99, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 99, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Evaluation of Wage Data for Interarea Comparisons, 1964; Publication (Box 99, Folder 29)
- Box: 99, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 99, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Royal Commission on Trade Unions and Employers' Associations, 1966; Publication (Box 99, Folder 30)
    Author: Royal Commission on Trade Unions and Employers' Associations
- Box: 99, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 99, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Compilation of Occupational Wage Data, Publication (Box 99, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: How to Make an Area Wage and Policies Survey, Publication (Box 99, Folder 31)
  - Item 3: How to Conduct a Salary Survey, 1948; Publication (Box 99, Folder 31)
    Author: National Office Management Association
  - Item 4: Community Approach to Wage Studies', Publication (Box 99, Folder 31)
  - Item 5: Policies and Procedures for Wage Surveys, 1947; Publication (Box 99, Folder 31)
    Author: Industrial Relations Committee
    Notes: March 14, 1947
  - Item 6: Area Practice Wage and Salary Surveys, Publication (Box 99, Folder 31)
    Author: Standard Oil Company
  - Item 7: Area Practice Wage and Salary Surveys, Publication (Box 99, Folder 31)
- Box: 99, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 99, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Types and Sources of Wage Data in Illinois, Publication (Box 99, Folder 32)
    Author: University of Illinois
- Box: 99, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 99, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: A Note on Labour, Wages and Rent, 1969; Publication (Box 99, Folder 33)
    Author: Gideon Rosenbluth
  - Item 2: Marginal Productivity Theory, Publication (Box 99, Folder 33)
  - Item 3: Unionism and Wage-Income Ratios, Publication (Box 99, Folder 33)
- Box: 99, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 99, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Wages, Prices and the National Welfare, Publication (Box 99, Folder 34)
  - Item 2: Union Wage Policy and Employment, 1948; Publication (Box 99, Folder 34)
    Author: Indiana Chamber of Commerce
    Notes: February 26, 1948
  - Item 3: Trade Unionism in Relation to Wages, Publication (Box 99, Folder 34)
    Author: James Birks
- Box: 99, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 99, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Gearing Wages to Productivity, Publication (Box 99, Folder 35)
    Author: Allen W. Rucker
- Box: 99, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 99, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Wage Policy and Economic Development, 1962; Publication (Box 99, Folder 36)
    Author: Manchester Statistical Society
    Notes: December 12, 1962
- Box: 99, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 99, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Everything You Need to Know About the Wage-Hour Rules, Publication (Box 99, Folder 37)
  - Item 2: The Guide for Wages Today, Publication (Box 99, Folder 37)
    Author: Macalester College
  - Item 3: How to Comply with Pay Control Procedures, Publication (Box 99, Folder 37)
    Author: William L. Davidson
- Box: 99, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 99, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Employment, Hour, and Earning of Production Workers, Publication (Box 99, Folder 38)
    Author: U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics
- Box: 99, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 99, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Summary of Earnings and Wage Rate Series, 1951; Publication (Box 99, Folder 39)
    Notes: July 1951
- Box: 99, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 99, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Wage Patterns, 1963; Publication (Box 99, Folder 40)
    Notes: April 19, 1963
- Box: 99, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 99, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: BLS Reports on Wage Developments, Publication (Box 99, Folder 41)
  - Item 2: Wages, Prices, and Profits, 1949; Publication (Box 99, Folder 41)
    Notes: September 1949
- Box: 99, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 99, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Report, Publication (Box 99, Folder 42)
  - Item 2: Amending the Employment Act to Provide for Price-Wage Guideposts, 1970; Publication (Box 99, Folder 42)
    Notes: May 25, 1970
- Box: 99, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 99, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: What is Pushing Up Prices and Holding Back Progress?, 1968; Publication (Box 99, Folder 43)
    Author: Channing L. Bete Co.
  - Item 2: Shift in the Wage-Price Climate?, 1964; Publication (Box 99, Folder 43)
    Author: Bankers Trust Company
    Notes: October 1, 1964
- Box: 99, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 99, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Guideline Policy, 1966; Publication (Box 99, Folder 44)
    Author: Arthur M. Ross
    Notes: April 27-28, 1966
  - Item 2: Wage, Price, and Productivity Statistics, 1964; Publication (Box 99, Folder 44)
  - Item 3: A Note on Labour, 1969; Publication (Box 99, Folder 44)
    Author: University of British Columbia
  - Item 4: Price-Wage Guideposts, 1969; Publication (Box 99, Folder 44)
  - Item 5: The Wage-Price Issue, 1968; Publication (Box 99, Folder 44)
    Notes: January 31, 1968
  - Item 6: Guideposts for Wages and Prices, 1968; Publication (Box 99, Folder 44)
    Author: Edward F. Denison
  - Item 7: A Unionist's Program to Meet Inflationary Threat, Publication (Box 99, Folder 44)
    Author: Solomon Barkin
  - Item 8: Progress Against Inflation, 1960; Publication (Box 99, Folder 44)
    Author: National Industrial Conference Board
  - Item 9: The Wage-Price Issue, 1968; Publication (Box 99, Folder 44)
  - Item 10: Wages, Prices, and Employment, Publication (Box 99, Folder 44)
    Author: Arther Butler
- Box: 99, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 99, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Wage/Price Policies, 1972; Publication (Box 99, Folder 45)
    Author: Committee for Economic Development of Australia
- Box: 99, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 99, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Labour Costs in Canada, 1966; Publication (Box 99, Folder 46)
    Author: Canadian Labour Congress
- Box: 99, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 99, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Deferred Wage Increases and Escalator Clauses, Publication (Box 99, Folder 47)
  - Item 2: Escalator Clauses, 1961; Publication (Box 99, Folder 47)
- Box: 99, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 99, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: The European Experience with Income and Price Policies, 1967; Publication (Box 99, Folder 48)
    Author: Permanent Technical Committee on Labor Matters
- Box: 99, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 99, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Lohn, Inflation und Zahlungsbilanz, Publication (Box 99, Folder 49)
    Author: Friedrich A. Lutz
- Box: 100, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Incomes Policy and the Individual, Publication (Box 100, Folder 1)
    Author: Oliver & Boyd
  - Item 2: The Great Wage Freeze Trick, Publication (Box 100, Folder 1)
    Author: Bert Ramelson
  - Item 3: Prices and Incomes Policy, 1965; Publication (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Productivity, 1968; Publication (Box 100, Folder 1)
    Notes: April 1968
  - Item 5: Cost or Demand Inflation?, Publication (Box 100, Folder 1)
    Author: L.A. Dicks-Mireaux
  - Item 6: Pay, Prices and Labour in Power, 1969; Publication (Box 100, Folder 1)
    Author: Fabian Pamphlets
  - Item 7: Freeze, Publication (Box 100, Folder 1)
    Author: John Marshall
  - Item 8: Trade Unions and an Incomes Policy, Publication (Box 100, Folder 1)
    Author: Economist Intelligence Unit
  - Item 9: Incomes Policy, Publication (Box 100, Folder 1)
- Box: 100, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Determinants of Wage Inflation in Ireland, 1966; Publication (Box 100, Folder 2)
    Author: Keith Cowling
- Box: 100, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Wages, Costs and Prices, 1962; Publication (Box 100, Folder 3)
- Box: 100, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Wage Policy and Wage Fixing Machinery in the Netherlands, Publication (Box 100, Folder 4)
- Box: 100, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Wages and Prices in an Industrial Economy, Publication (Box 100, Folder 5)
- Box: 100, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Industry in Rural Wales, Publication (Box 100, Folder 6)
    Author: Roy Thomas
- Box: 100, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: An Analysis of Sick Leave Practices and Longevity Pay Systems in Washington State Government, 1964; Publication (Box 100, Folder 7)
    Author: Washington Personnel Board
- Box: 100, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Enlisting Employees in Waste Reduction, Publication (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: How to Cut Waste, Publication (Box 100, Folder 8)
    Author: Glenn Gardiner
- Box: 100, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Industrialization and the Distribution of Wealth in Peru, 1966; Publication (Box 100, Folder 9)
    Author: David Chaplin
- Box: 100, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: New Disclosure Requirements, Publication (Box 100, Folder 10)
- Box: 100, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: For and Against the Welfare State Swedish Experiences, 1963; Publication (Box 100, Folder 11)
    Author: The Swedish Institute
- Box: 100, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Program Facts, 1970; Publication (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Trends in AFDC, Publication (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Managing the Intake Process in Income Maintenance, Publication (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Toward Community, Publication (Box 100, Folder 12)
- Box: 100, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Welfare Among Dock Workers, Publication (Box 100, Folder 13)
    Author: National Dock Labour Board
  - Item 2: People and Work, 1960; Publication (Box 100, Folder 13)
    Author: National Council of Social Service
- Box: 100, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Servicio Social Industrial, Publication (Box 100, Folder 14)
    Author: Union Panamericana
- Box: 100, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Impact of the West Coast Maritime Strike, 1962; Publication (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Impact of the West Coast Maritime Strike, 1963; Publication (Box 100, Folder 15)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Merchant Marine and Fisheries
    Notes: March 19, 1963
  - Item 3: The Maritime Industry on the Atlantic and Gulf Coast, 1963; Publication (Box 100, Folder 15)
    Notes: February 20, 1963
- Box: 100, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Nationalism and Industrial Development, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    Author: University College of the West Indies
- Box: 100, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The Economy, Publication (Box 100, Folder 17)
    Author: West Virginia Department of Employment Security
- Box: 100, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: County Study Data Book, 1961; Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
    Author: West Virginia University
    Notes: August 1961
- Box: 100, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The University Bookman, 1971; Publication (Box 100, Folder 19)
    Author: The University Bookman
    Notes: Winter 1971
- Box: 100, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 100, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Practices for White-Collar Employees, 1963; Publication (Box 100, Folder 20)
    Notes: May 1963
- Box: 100, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 100, Folder 21)